Believe the impossible.
Little Boy is a comedy, drama, war film directed by Alejandro Monteverde.
An eight-year-old boy is willing to do whatever it takes to end
World War II so he can bring his father home.
The story reveals the indescribable love a father has for his
little boy and the love a son has for his father.
Pepper Flynt Busbee / Little Boy, played by Jakob Salvati.
Emma Busbee, played by Emily Watson.
Hashimoto, played by Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa.
James Busbee, played by Michael Rapaport.
London Busbee, played by David Henrie.
Ben Eagle, played by Ben Chaplin.
Little Boy is a 2015 World War II war-drama film
directed by Alejandro Gómez Monteverde.
The screenplay is by Monteverde and Pepe Portillo, and the film was produced by Eduardo
Verástegui and Leo Severino, and edited by Joan Sobel and Fernando Villena.
The film stars Jakob Salvati, Emily Watson, David Henrie, Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa, Michael Rapaport, Ben Chaplin,
Eduardo Verástegui, Ted Levine, Abraham Benrubi, Toby Huss, Kevin James, and Tom Wilkinson.
The title is a reference to Little Boy, the code name for the atomic bomb dropped on
Hiroshima, as well as a reference to the main character Pepper's height.
The film was co-produced by Metanoia Films and Santa Fé Films and
was released on April 24, 2015, by Open Road Films.
It was released on DVD and Blu-ray on August 18, 2015, by
Universal Pictures Home Entertainment.
The film received negative reviews from mainstream critics and
earned $17 million on a $20 million budget.
An Indian adaptation of the film, titled Tubelight and starring Salman Khan
in the lead role, also opened to negative reviews in 2017.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.